greece-is.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Greece Is

**PERSONAL DATA PRIVACY POLICY-COOKIES**

 **PROTECTION POLICY**

The management and protection of the personal data of a visitor or user of the Website is subject to the relevant provisions of Greek law (Law 2472/1997 on protection of individuals and protection of personal data, as supplemented and in force).

This Policy refers to the ways in which KATHIMERINES collects, holds, and uses personally identifiable information.

 **BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY KATHIMERINES AS SET OUT IN THIS PERSONAL DATA PRIVACY POLICY.**

 **YOU ALSO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT KATHIMERINES MAY PERIODICALLY CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD, REMOVE, OR ADVISE IN ANY WAY THIS PERSONAL DATA MANAGEMENT POLICY AT ITS SOLE DISCRETION, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE.**

Our intention is to communicate any changes on this page so that you are always informed about the type of information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we might disclose it.

 **Guarantee of Private Use**

The term “personal data”, as used herein, refers to information such as name, date of birth, postal or email address, which can be used to identify you.

KATHIMERINES will not process your personal data without your consent. However, we reserve the right, in exceptional cases, to process data to the extent permitted or required by law.

In the event that disclosure of personal data to a third party is necessary for any reason, KATHIMERINES will inform you, and will make every effort, when possible, to ensure that the processing of data is in accordance with the purpose and within the limits set out at the beginning of data collection. There are two additional cases in which your personal data may be transmitted to third parties. First, the case of sale, concession, or assignment of the site and the customer data connected to it, which, in any case, will require the purchaser, the person to whom the concession is made, or the transferee to comply with this Personal Data Management Policy. Second, the case where any disclosure of personal data to a third party is required by law, court decision/order, government/administrative act, or due to an investigation.

 **Right of Access**

You have the right to be assured that, in all cases, your personal data will always be up to date. Furthermore, you have the right to request that it be corrected or deleted. Moreover, at any time, you can request that we cease contact and communication with you.

If you wish to contact us to inquire about the use of your personal data or to deny any use thereof, you may reach us at the following mail : WELCOME@GREECE-IS.COM When contacting us, please indicate your full name as well as what specific information you wish to be corrected, amended, or deleted. Your requests will be addressed promptly and properly. Requests for deletion of data are subject to all provisions of law and ethics with regard to obligations of maintenance and storage, which are binding on KATHIMERINES.

 **COOKIES**

During a first visit to or use of KATHIMERINES’s Website, information tokens widely known as “cookies” may be placed on the user’s computer. The Website uses “cookies”, which are necessary to identify and/or maintain content entered by the subscriber or user during a session to the site throughout the duration of the session.

Any website may send a cookie to your browser, if your browser settings allow it. Only in case a website sends to you tracking cookies for the first time, you shall be notified so as to accept the cookies. A browser allows a website to access only the cookies that it has sent you, not the cookies sent from other websites.

Such “cookies” will be sent automatically from the user’s computer to KATHIMERINES’s website every time the user chooses to revisit this website.

 **Practices of this website regarding user IDs and cookies** With respect to cookies and the manner of their use, this website holds session cookies, which are deleted after the end of your browsing session. This website uses cookies for the purpose of carrying out transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network, which is necessary for the supply of services in an information society.

The cookies provide information regarding the manner and the time that a user visited this web site, while allowing KATHIMERINES to oversee how many users in total have visited its website. This technology collects information en masse, as a whole, and does not collect personal information which would enable the identification of specific persons. KATHIMERINES hopes to improve the quality of the Website through information collected using this method.

 **IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO RECEIVE COOKIES**

You can configure your computer so that it warns you every time a cookie is sent to it, or disable the receipt of all cookies through your Internet browser (e.g. Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator). (Check the Help menu in your browser to learn how to properly change or update settings related to cookies.)
